JUAN C. BARRIOS S.

FRONT END DEVELOPER

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

JavaScript
TypeScript
React
Next
Tailwind
Flutter
React Native

PERSONAL SKILLS

Creative
Trustworthy and professional
Organized
Time management
Teamwork
Fast learner
Motivated

CONTACT

+58 4121556808 juanbarrios045@gmail.com https://juanbarrios.vercel.com/

REFERENCES

LENNON PEREZ

Front End Developer lenonart14@gmail.com

JUNIOR SÁNCHEZ

Developer FullStack jysa65.dev@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

My name is Juan, I'm 23 years old and I'm from Venezuela. I am a big fan of web development and technology. I am passionate about working as a Front End Developer and I always make sure that what I develop is perfect. I am great at working in a team and I adjust to everything you need.

I'm a Front End Developer with more than five year of work experience.

EXPERIENCE

FITHUB

August 2024 - Present

Responsible for supporting the website (an ecommerce) as a frontend developer using React, Tailwind with Twin Macro, and SEO.

MONOMA

March 2024 - July 2024

Responsible for supporting several web projects using Next and React, Tailwind and testing

ASP CONSULTING

May 2023 - March 2024

Responsible for supporting several mobile applications about point of sale using React Native and SDK natives connected with a bridge native

TAUROS

Nov 2019 - Feb 2023

Responsible for supporting a robust web site about cryptocurrency with an exchange, I worked with React, Material UI, and couple months with React Native

FREELANCER

Sep 2019 - Present

Providing website or mobile app creation services, consulting and classes, I have created more than 15 websites as a freelancer using Next with Tailwind

EDUCATION

SYSTEMS ANALYST

Instituto Universitario de Tecnología para la informatica (IUTEPI) 2017 - 2020